You know, I like my **Fridays black** and **Mondays cyber**

50% OFF

Use code**MYFRIDAY2024**

Products

Get Started

[

Twitter Management

Twitter management tool](https://login.circleboom.com/oauth2/register?tenantId=046a5cb0-7b85-c8c2-dc2e-1109f8773fe6&client_id=e1044da0-14db-4200-9f1c-1ef7f3d49502&redirect_uri=https%3A%2F%2Ftwitter.circleboom.com%2Foauth-redirect&response_type=code&state=569iqch5iib23rh4cc461axer8gjbjqdhvotcypnj2k87v7xmyb0dt4uql14v46chl)[

Publish

Social media management tool](https://login.circleboom.com/oauth2/register?tenantId=046a5cb0-7b85-c8c2-dc2e-1109f8773fe6&client_id=0969b30c-f71c-40f8-9905-2be8ec8667d4&redirect_uri=https%3A%2F%2Fpublish.circleboom.com%2Foauth-redirect&response_type=code&state=569iqch5iib23rh4cc461axer8gjbjqdhvotcypnj2k87v7xmyb0dt4uql14v46chl)

Get Started

[

Twitter Management

Twitter management tool](https://login.circleboom.com/oauth2/register?tenantId=046a5cb0-7b85-c8c2-dc2e-1109f8773fe6&client_id=e1044da0-14db-4200-9f1c-1ef7f3d49502&redirect_uri=https%3A%2F%2Ftwitter.circleboom.com%2Foauth-redirect&response_type=code&state=569iqch5iib23rh4cc461axer8gjbjqdhvotcypnj2k87v7xmyb0dt4uql14v46chl)[

Publish

Social media management tool](https://login.circleboom.com/oauth2/register?tenantId=046a5cb0-7b85-c8c2-dc2e-1109f8773fe6&client_id=0969b30c-f71c-40f8-9905-2be8ec8667d4&redirect_uri=https%3A%2F%2Fpublish.circleboom.com%2Foauth-redirect&response_type=code&state=569iqch5iib23rh4cc461axer8gjbjqdhvotcypnj2k87v7xmyb0dt4uql14v46chl)

Privacy Policy
==============

Last revised on: June 5, 2024

Your privacy is of the utmost importance to us. At Circleboom, we want to make your experience online satisfying and safe.

Because we gather certain types of information about our users, we feel you should fully understand our policy and the terms and conditions surrounding the capture and use of that information. This privacy statement discloses what information we gather and how we use it.

Information Circleboom Gather and Tracks
----------------------------------------

##### Circleboom gathers three types of information about users:

* Information that users provide through optional, voluntary submissions. These are voluntary submissions to receive our electronic newsletters, to participate feedback forums and from participation in competitions and surveys:
* Information Circleboom gathers through aggregated tracking information derived mainly by tallying page views and actions performed throughout our sites. This information allows us to better tailor our features to users' needs and to help us better understand the demographics of our audience.
* Information collected from third party services for which you provide Circleboom with Twitter API access credentials. Information collected from these services will be used to provide you with functionality visible on Circleboom. We may also utilize this data in to produce aggregate reports such as infographics or to produce additional value added information such as influence ranking to the public.

##### Circleboom Gathers User Information in The Following Processes:

* Electronic newsletters policy  
    We will offer a free electronic newsletter to users. Circleboom gathers the email addresses of users who voluntarily subscribe. Users may remove themselves from this mailing list by following the link provided in every newsletter that points users to the subscription management page.
* Feedback forums  
    Users of the site's Feedback Forums must register separately for this service in order to post messages, although they needn't register to visit the site. During registration the user is required to supply a username, password, and email address.
* Twitter  
    User who connect their Twitter account with Circleboom should be aware that this provide us with full access via Twitter's API to the details contained in your Twitter account. This includes, but is not limited to; your entire tweet stream, all of your friends and followers, your account settings and your account details. This does not include your Direct Messages or password.  
      
    Circleboom will use this API access to provide you with the functionality on our website. We will collect information from this API about your social graph to provide you with unfollow tools. We will collect information from this API about your Tweet stream to provide Tweet related tools.  
      
    Circleboom may republish public information you provide in another public forum. This includes information about your Twitter account to provide influence ranking tools. We will never republish private information publicly and will always abide by Twitter's rules regarding Third Party Developers.  
      
    You can, at any time, revoke Circleboom's access to your Twitter account from your settings page on Twitter. You can also contact us and request we remove any information we have cached about you.  

* Google  
    Circleboom’s use and transfer to any other app of information received from Google APIs will adhere to [Google API Services User Data Policy](https://developers.google.com/terms/api-services-user-data-policy), including the Limited Use requirements.
* Competitions  
    We may offer optional voluntary competitions where we will collect explicit information which you provide. If you are currently logged into Circleboom we may track your entry to the competition with its connection to the Circleboom account.
* Surveys  
    Circleboom may occasionally conduct user surveys to better target our content to our audience. We sometimes share the aggregated demographic information in these surveys with our sponsors, advertisers and partners. We never share any of this information about specific individuals with any third party.
* Children  
    Consistent with the United State Federal Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA), we will never knowingly request personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13 without requesting parental consent. In order to use Circleboom, users must have a valid Twitter account.
* Usage tracking  
    Circleboom tracks user traffic patterns throughout all of our sites. However, we do not correlate this information with data about individual users. Circleboom does break down overall usage statistics according to a user's domain name, browser type, and MIME type by reading this information from the browser string (information contained in every user's browser).  
      
    Circleboom sometimes tracks and catalogs the search terms that users enter in our Search function. We use tracking information to determine which areas of our sites users like and don't like based on traffic to those areas. This helps us continue to build a better service for you.
* Cookies  
    We may place a text file called a "cookie" in the browser files of your computer. The cookie itself does not contain Personal Information although it will enable us to relate your use of this site to information that you have specifically and knowingly provided. But the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. Circleboom uses cookies to track user traffic patterns (as described above). Our advertising system delivers a one-time cookie to better track ad impressions and click rates.  
      
    You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser. If you've set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies, you will receive the warning message with each cookie. You do need cookies in order to use most of the functionality on this site.

Use of Information
------------------

Circleboom uses any information voluntarily given by our users to enhance their experience in our network of sites, whether to provide interactive or personalized elements on the sites or to better prepare future content based on the interests of our users.

As stated above, we use information that users voluntarily provide in order to send out electronic newsletters and to enable users to participate in polls, surveys, message boards, and forums. We send out newsletters to subscribers on a regular schedule (depending on the newsletter), and occasionally send out special editions when we think subscribers might be particularly interested in something we are doing. Circleboom never shares newsletter mailing lists with any third parties, including advertisers, sponsors or partners.

When we use tracking information to determine which areas of our sites users like and don't like based on traffic to those areas. We track search terms entered in Search function as one of many measures of what interests our users. Circleboom creates aggregate reports on user demographics and traffic patterns for advertisers, sponsors and partners. This allows our advertisers to advertise more effectively, and allows our users to receive advertisements that are pertinent to their needs. Because we don't track the usage patterns of individual users, an advertiser or sponsor will never know that a specific user clicked their ad. We may also disclose information about any individual user to comply with applicable law or valid legal process or to protect the personal safety of our users or the public.

Disclosure of Data to Third-Party Tools
---------------------------------------

As part of providing our services, we may share certain data with third-party tools, including AI models, analytics tools, and other services. These third-party tools help us to enhance the functionality of our platform, improve user experience, and perform essential services such as data analysis, customer support, and personalized recommendations.

We ensure that any third-party tool we integrate with complies with applicable data protection laws and maintains high standards of data security and privacy. The types of data shared and the purposes for which they are used are always limited to what is necessary to deliver our services effectively.

SHARING OF THE INFORMATION
--------------------------

Circleboom uses the above-described information to tailor our content to suit your needs and help our advertisers better understand our audience's demographics. This is essential to keeping our service free. We will not share any previously private information about individual users with any third party, except to comply with applicable law or valid legal process or to protect the personal safety of our users or the public.

SECURITY
--------

The security of your information is important to us. Circleboom has implemented safeguards to protect the information we collect. However, no website or Internet transmission is completely secure. We urge you to take steps to keep your personal information safe, such as choosing a strong password and keeping it private, as well as logging out of your user account, and closing your web browser when finished using the Circleboom on a shared or unsecured device.

OPT-OUT POLICY
--------------

We give users options wherever necessary and practical. Such choices include:

Opting not to register to receive our electronic newsletters.

Opting not to participate in certain interactive areas, which completely alleviates the need to gather any personally identifiable information from our users

You may contact us to have information we have cached about your from third party services removed from our system.

Additional Information for California Residents
-----------------------------------------------

This section provides information organized in accordance with the California Consumer Privacy Act (“CCPA”) for residents of California about how we handle certain personal information we have collected over the past 12 months.

**_Categories of Personal Information_**. This Privacy Policy discloses the categories of personal information that we collect, use, and disclose in order to operate our business over the past 12 months.

* **Collect**. The section above entitled **Information Circleboom Gather and Tracks** discloses the categories of personal information that we collect, which include your account and profile information, your content, your communications with us, your information you provide from linked networks, information about your activity on Circleboom, and how you engage with our Circleboom.
* **Use**. The section above entitled **Use of Information** discloses the that the categories of personal information we collect are used to provide our services, for personalization, to provide advertising in order to generate income to operate Circleboom, to promote our services to you, to analyze how our services are used, to comply with law, and to prevent misuse of Circleboom.
* **Disclose**. The section above entitled **Sharing of the Information** discloses that we share your personal information with, service providers, affiliates, law enforcement authorities, and as needed with third parties to provide our services.

**_We do not sell your personal information to third parties_**. Circleboom may share your personal information with third parties and third parties may collect your personal information as described above in the **Sharing of the Information** section. In addition, we may also work with third parties such as network advertisers to serve ads on Circleboom and on third-party websites or other media (e.g., social networking platforms), such as Google AdSense (more info [here)](https://support.google.com/adsense/answer/142293?hl=en) and Facebook Audience Network (more info [here](https://www.facebook.com/help/568137493302217)). These third parties may use cookies, JavaScript, web beacons (including clear GIFs), Flash LSOs and other tracking technologies to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content to you.

We do not collect personal information from consumers that we know are younger than 16 years old.

Requests for Deletion, Copy and Right to Know Your Information
--------------------------------------------------------------

California consumers have the right to make the following requests, which we endeavor to honor from non-California residents as well:

* **Deletion**. You have the right to request deletion of personal information that we have collected about you.
* **Copy and Right to Know**. You have the right to request a copy of the specific pieces of personal information that we have collected about you over the past 12 months, including the categories of information, sources, and purposes of collection, as well as categories of third parties we have shared it with.
* **Designated Agent**. You may designate an agent to make a request on your behalf. That agent must have access to your account in order for us to verify the request.

You can submit a deletion, copy and right to know request by emailing us at [\[email protected\]](https://circleboom.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection). You will need access to the email account associated with your Circleboom account in order to verify your identity and complete this process.

**_Non-Discrimination_**. Circleboom will not discriminate against you, including by denying or providing a different level or quality of goods or services should you choose to exercise your options under the CCPA.

**_Your California Privacy Rights under California’s Shine-the-Light Law_**. California law permits users who are California residents to request and obtain from us once a year, free of charge, a list of the third parties to whom we have disclosed their personal information (if any) for their direct marketing purposes in the prior calendar year, as well as the types of personal information disclosed to those parties. If you are a California resident and would like to request this information, please submit your request in an email to [\[email protected\]](https://circleboom.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

Contact Us
----------

If you have any questions about our practices or this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [\[email protected\]](https://circleboom.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

YOUR CONSENT
------------

By using this site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by Circleboom. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

##### Circleboom, Boom your social circle!

* PUBLISH TOOL

* TWITTER TOOL

* About

Copyright © 2017-2024 Circleboom llc, all rights reserved.
